<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>Cool Straw - News</title>
  <updated>2021-03-11T11:37:42-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Cool Straw</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news/and-then-2020-pandemic</id>
    <published>2021-03-11T11:37:42-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-11T11:39:40-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news/and-then-2020-pandemic"/>
    <title>And then 2020.....Pandemic</title>
    <author>
      <name>Liz McCutcheon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Well who would have added "Pandemic" to their business plan?</p>
<p>Certainly not me. </p>
<p>At the time this news hit the world, I was selling product in a busy retail store, I had over 100 market events booked and things were rolling nicely!</p>
<p>1000's products getting into the hands of Eager Zero Wasters was like music to our ears. Were now accomplishing what we set out to do!</p>
<p>STOP.</p>
<p>All changed with the announcement of World Wide Pandemic and particularly for us Ontario Lockdowns. The world has changed. Major pre-cautions were put into place everywhere. </p>
<p>The business all but stopped.</p>
<p>We'll ride this temporary restriction out as it was initially a couple of weeks of lock-down and all will resume again. Right? Wrong.</p>
<p>Weeks turned into months.</p>
<p>Face to face markets /selling turned to on-line sales, they are great of course but just not the same amount of fun, connecting with community &amp; customers. The educating for new ways to save / recycle/ re-use was gone.</p>
<p>Staying optimistic the Good Old Days will return!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news/what-did-we-accomplish-in-2019</id>
    <published>2021-03-11T11:13:46-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-11T11:13:48-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news/what-did-we-accomplish-in-2019"/>
    <title>What did we accomplish in 2019?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Liz McCutcheon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Well proudly we accomplished a-lot for a small business.</p>
<p>Many more products were added as we can't change the environment issue just with steel straws! </p>
<p>Bamboo toothbrushes, pot scrubbers, dish cloths etc as well as facial products and wheat straw products too!</p>
<p>Mom markets, farmer's markets and hospital vendor programs have been a huge success with folks so excited to FINALLY find affordable sustainable products.</p>
<p>This business has taken true form and beyond satisfying.</p>
<p>It's alot of fun to be face to face and seeing the changing habits right before my eyes. If it's just one product at at time....it's shifting and this is truly exciting!</p>
<p>Each week as our recycling, garbage waste dwindles away it's become a true family challenge to get as close to ZERO WASTE as possible.</p>
<p>Is it truly possible?</p>
<p>Bea Johnson did it......except for a small mason jar collected over 1 YEAR! and this was done with her family of 4! </p>
<p>It's a lifestyle change....lifestyle meaning it will never go away this desire and need to change our ways.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news/it-started-with-a-single-straw</id>
    <published>2021-03-11T11:00:09-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-11T11:03:06-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://coolstraw.ca/blogs/news/it-started-with-a-single-straw"/>
    <title>It started with a Single Steel Straw</title>
    <author>
      <name>Liz McCutcheon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p> </p>
<p>I've always been frugal with spending, managing food waste and conscious of volume of garbage / recycling in my home.</p>
<p>I'm seeing more and more reports, videos from around the world, introduction to Bea Johnson's Zero Waste Lifestyle book, Greta Thunberg activism and thought.....what can I do to help?</p>
<p>I placed an order for 1,000 steel straws.</p>
<p>Now what do I do?</p>
<p>And so it began, Cool Straw - straw supplier to replace plastic straws.</p>
<p>With an order of 1,000 straws, I started Facebook / Instagram pages and looked for ways to sell these straws.</p>
<p>Of course, with my own family, the straws were a happy site and easily adaptable utensil.  Of course the more colourful, collapsible, twisty the better for the little ones.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
